<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<data>
    <topic name="Animal Things">
        <note name="Dogs are better than cats 03">
            <text>
            Dogs respond when you call their name (unlike cats, who just ignore you)
            </text>
            <timestamp>
            03/16/21 - 14:03:04
            </timestamp>
        </note>
    <note name="Horseys"><text>I just want to pet their cute snouts c:</text><timestamp>29/03/2021 - 15:02:12</timestamp></note><note name="Fishes"><text>They have such cute little eyes :)</text><timestamp>29/03/2021 - 15:32:11</timestamp></note></topic>
<topic name="Television"><note name="Wikipedia entry on 'Teletubbies'"><text>Teletubbies is a British children's television series created by Anne Wood and Andrew Davenport for the BBC. The programme focuses on four differently coloured creatures known as "Teletubbies", named after the television screens implanted in their abdomens. Recognised throughout popular culture for the uniquely shaped antenna protruding from the head of each character, the Teletubbies communicate through gibberish and were designed to bear resemblance to toddlers.The series rapidly became a commercial success in Britain and abroad. It won multiple BAFTA awards and was nominated for two Daytime Emmys throughout its run. A single based on the show's theme song reached number 1 in the UK Singles Chart in December 1997 and remained in the Top 75 for 32 weeks, selling over a million copies. By October 2000, the franchise generated over £1 billion ($1.6 billion) in merchandise sales.Though the original run ended in 2001, sixty new episodes were ordered in 2014. They are currently aired on CBeebies in the United Kingdom and on Nick Jr. in the United States. Re-runs of the original 1997–2001 series continue to be shown on television channels worldwide.
The original series returned to live TV in the US on Pluto TV on 1 May 2019 but the episodes are shown in the UK format instead of the US which is where the Pluto TV service is based. The same error occurred with the series' availability on the NOGGIN app since 25 May 2016.</text><timestamp>29/03/2021 - 15:02:50</timestamp></note><note name="Wikipedia entry on 'Teletubbies'"><text>Teletubbies is a British children's television series created by Anne Wood and Andrew Davenport for the BBC. The programme focuses on four differently coloured creatures known as "Teletubbies", named after the television screens implanted in their abdomens. Recognised throughout popular culture for the uniquely shaped antenna protruding from the head of each character, the Teletubbies communicate through gibberish and were designed to bear resemblance to toddlers.The series rapidly became a commercial success in Britain and abroad. It won multiple BAFTA awards and was nominated for two Daytime Emmys throughout its run. A single based on the show's theme song reached number 1 in the UK Singles Chart in December 1997 and remained in the Top 75 for 32 weeks, selling over a million copies. By October 2000, the franchise generated over £1 billion ($1.6 billion) in merchandise sales.Though the original run ended in 2001, sixty new episodes were ordered in 2014. They are currently aired on CBeebies in the United Kingdom and on Nick Jr. in the United States. Re-runs of the original 1997–2001 series continue to be shown on television channels worldwide.
The original series returned to live TV in the US on Pluto TV on 1 May 2019 but the episodes are shown in the UK format instead of the US which is where the Pluto TV service is based. The same error occurred with the series' availability on the NOGGIN app since 25 May 2016.</text><timestamp>29/03/2021 - 15:36:59</timestamp></note></topic><topic name="Games"><note name="Wikipedia entry on 'Minecraft Dungeons'"><text>Minecraft Dungeons is a dungeon crawler video game developed by Mojang Studios and Double Eleven and published by Xbox Game Studios. It is a spin-off of the sandbox video game Minecraft and was released for Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, Windows, and Xbox One on May 26, 2020. The game received mixed reviews; many deemed the game fun and charming, with praise for its visuals and music. However, its simple gameplay and use of procedural generation were met with a more mixed reception, with its short story and lack of depth criticized.

</text><timestamp>29/03/2021 - 15:39:19</timestamp></note><note name="Wikipedia entry on 'Risk of Rain 2'"><text>Risk of Rain 2 is a roguelike third-person shooter developed by Hopoo Games and published by Gearbox Publishing. A sequel to 2013's Risk of Rain, it was released in early access for Microsoft Windows, and Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4 and Xbox One in 2019 before fully releasing on August 11, 2020 with a release for Stadia coming a month later.
Players control a survivor who is stranded on an alien planet. To survive, they navigate through various environments, killing monsters and looting chests to collect items that boost their offensive and defensive capabilities. Over time, the game's difficulty increases, spawning more powerful and dangerous creatures. The game supports up to four players in online multiplayer. The game received generally positive reviews upon release.</text><timestamp>29/03/2021 - 15:39:20</timestamp></note></topic></data>